你好 我是今晚的服务生
hi, I'm gonna be your waitress,
谁让我妈是不争气的酒鬼呢
'cause my mother drank.
稍等一下
We need a sec.
姐大方点 等你们两下好了
Feeling' kinda generous, take two.
他对我说"妹子 你的阴道长得也太奇葩了"
Then he said to me, "dude, your vagina is weird."
他也太扯了吧
Dude, that's insane.
你那里一点都不奇葩啊
It is so not weird.
你的阴道棒呆了
Your vagina's awesome.
好了 我可以点餐了
Okay, I'm ready.
现在换你们等我一下
Now I need a sec.
好了 一切玩完了
Well, it's over.
那个词我再也不能说了
I can't say it anymore.
阴道变成流行词汇了
The vagina's gone mainstream.
接下来呢 在百货公司推出服装品牌吗
What's next? A clothing line at Target?
麦克斯 我也替你难过
Aw, Max, I'm sorry.
那可是你最爱的词
It's your favorite word.
那也是我最爱的部位
And my favorite body part.
可现在人人都把它挂嘴边
But now everyone's saying it.
我们可以换个词来替代它嘛
Well, we can pick another word for it.
想个可爱点的 比如"小饼干"
Something cute, like cookie.
是啊 乍听之下还可以
Yeah, it sounds like a good idea
但哪天你碰到一群在大街上卖
Until you walk past a bunch of girl scouts
"小饼干"的女童军就尴尬了
selling their cookies on the street.
我们还是得找个新词
Well, we've gotta pick something,
毕竟"阴道"已经烂大街了
'cause vagina's everywhere.
哪条街
Where?
《打工姐妹花》前情回顾
Previously on 2 broke girls...
这是大都会博物馆年度晚会的邀请函
This is invitation to metropolitan museum annual gala.
我们有邀请函 她又会在场
We have the invitation. She'll be there.
你是说我们去跟踪玛莎·斯图尔特吗
You are talking about us stalking Martha Stewart.
所以你要我在女厕所吃你的小蛋糕吗
So you want me to taste your cupcake in the ladies' room?
还有比这更不合时宜的吗
What's inappropriate about that?
这是我们的酒混面粉
That is our beer batter
加枫蜜培根的特制春假小蛋糕
maple bacon spring break cupcake.
蛮好吃的
Quite tasty.
你们有名片吗
Do you girls have a card?
玛莎·斯图尔特喜欢我们的小蛋糕
Martha Stewart likes our cupcakes!
麦克斯 你看见我的手机了吗
Max, have you seen my phone?
我要把这点少得可怜的小费拍下来
I wanna take a picture of this bad tip
然后放到图片分享网
and put it on Instagram.
以前收到这么散的零钱会难过
Getting loose change used to be so depressing,
但是现在我可以跟陌生人分享一下
but now I can share it with strangers.
我来总结一下
Let me sum it up.
推特已经够蠢了
Twitter is stupid.
而图片分享网 就是给不识字的人看的推特
And Instagram is twitter for people who can't read.
我的手机在哪儿
Where is my phone?
我发誓我把它放在你手机旁边了
I could've sworn I left it right here, next to yours.
我打个电话就知道了
Oh, I'll just call it.
没必要吧
Oh, that's not necessary.
它会自己跑出来的...
I'm sure it'll turn up...
老娘的"奶"昔招蜂引蝶一流 *
* My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard
随便一比都比姐们你牛 *
* and there like it's better than yours
在我口袋里
In my pocket.
麦克斯 你干嘛把我手机藏在你围裙里
Max, why are you hiding my phone in your apron?
这不是重点 好吗
Is that the big question, really?
我觉得重点是
'cause I think the bigger question is,
你的铃音为什么会是
Why is your ringtone
"老娘的"奶"昔招蜂引蝶一流"
"my milkshake brings all the boys to the yard"?
如果连这你都不知道
If you have to ask that,
那想必你是没看见过我的"奶昔"
You clearly have not seen my milkshake.
好吧 还给你 被你逮到了
Okay, here. I'm busted.
我检查玛莎·斯图尔特给我们打电话了没
I was checking to see if Martha Stewart called us yet.
你又检查啊
You checked it again?
你每15分钟就要看一遍
You check it, like, every 15 minutes.
是啊 我现在就像个没骨气的妞
I know! I am acting like a little bitch.
麦克斯 玛莎·斯图尔特有我们的名片
Max, Martha Stewart has our business card.
她喜欢我们的小蛋糕 她就会打电话
She liked our cupcakes. She'll call.
我想说的是 是她先开口要的名片
Look, in my defense, she asked for our card.
把我们搞得既兴奋又期待 然后呢
She got us all hot and bothered. And then what?
音讯全无
Nothing.
玛莎·斯图尔特敢说不敢做
Martha Stewart is a cake tease.
你好大的胆子
How dare you!
玛莎·斯图尔特才不是敢说不敢做呢
Martha Stewart is not a cake tease.
敢说不敢做的人最差劲了
Nothing worse than a cake tease.
不信你随便找个男人问问
Ask any man.
你兴冲冲沐浴更衣 还给蛋蛋擦香香
Yeah, you shower, you powder your sack.
不给搞算毛啊
For what?
麦克斯 别紧张 她会打给我们的
Look, Max, relax. She'll call.
一切都会水到渠成的
Everything's gonna work out.
一年以前
I mean, a year ago,
我们连小蛋糕事业都没有
we didn't even have a cupcake business.
现在进步了这么多 不爽吗
Look how far we've come.
全怪那个敢说不敢做的人
I haven't come at all,
我一点"爽"感都没有
thanks to the cake tease.
你们的小蛋糕真好吃
Oh, your cupcake is quite tasty.
你们有名片吗
Do you have a card?
麦克斯 你学她可真像
Max, that's a good Martha Stewart.
我知道 因为我忘不掉她蛊惑人的声音
I know, 'cause I can't get her siren voice out of my head.
哎哟 小憨憨
Wow, Han.
你就像被一辆狂欢节花车撞完
You look you were hit by a mardi gras
然后又被一辆男同游行彩车撞到
and a gay pride float.
我刚从激动人心的
I have just returned from the exciting
曼哈顿餐馆贸易展览归来
Manhattan restaurant trade show.
快看这些免费的赠品
Look at all this free swag.
我还拿了很多减压球
And I've got stress balls.
那你去后面好好"自己玩"吧
Well, just go in the back and take care of yourself.
各位听着
Listen up, everybody.
我有大事宣布
I have a big announcement.
哪能多大 顶多一米六
Well, more like a 5'1 annoucement.
我要把餐厅改造现代化的餐厅
I am changing the diner to state-of-the-art
点餐和结账采用电脑智慧触控式系统
computer "Power touch" ordering system for food and checks.
我才不学什么新东西呢
I am not learning anything new.
老娘来这上班 就是因为没啥能力
I work here because I have no skills.
这系统不必学 麦克斯
You don't have to learn it, Max.
它是台很智能的机器
It's very smart machine.
它会帮你的
It will help you.
《黑客帝国》里的机器一开始也是那样啊
That's how it started with machines in The Matrix.
结果很快人类就变成了电脑的奴隶
Next thing you know, the human race was enslaved.
我亲身体验过了
Been there, done that.
我支持麦克斯
I'm with Max.
不行也得行
We are doing it.
让生意与未来接轨是十分重要的
It's important to move the business into the future.
慢慢习惯吧 卢德分子们
So get with it, you Luddites.
姑娘们 咱们有麻烦啦
Girls, we got big trouble.
他要是搞了这个新系统
If he starts using a new system,
我就没办法用以前的系统
I won't be to use my old system,
也就表示没办法捞油水了
where I skim somethig of the top.
厄尔 捞油水吗
Earl, skimming?
我真不敢相信你会这样
I'm kind of shocked.
我又不是为了自己
I don't do it for me.
你们俩不是每个月都会
You know how once a month you girls
有个小费满满的夜晚吗
have a really good night in tips?
大恩不言谢 记心里就行
You are welcome.
我那晚整宿睡不着 就是想不明白
I have been lying awake at night trying to figure out
就她那样 我们怎么可能赚那么多小费
how we made that 200 bucks with her skills.
-姑娘们 -你好啊 苏菲
- Hey, girls. - Hey, Sophie.
我每次来光顾都在惊讶
You know, every time I come here,
你们店怎么还没倒闭
I'm surprised you're still open.
给 苏菲
Here you go, Sophie.
那个每次都给我递菜单的
Where's the little asian woman
小亚洲姑娘哪去了
That always hands me my menu?
亚洲姑娘
Asian woman?
你是说阿憨吗
You mean Han?
苏菲 阿憨是男的
Sophie, Han's a man.
你说是就是吧
If you say so.
今晚有什么特别菜吗
Is there anything special tonight?
有的
Yes.
特别菜来也
Here I am...
还带了礼物给我的小甜心
with treats for my sweet.
荧光斑马纹
Day-glo zebra?
我最爱斑马了
That's my favorite animal.
可食用内衣裤
Oh, and edible underwear!
那是我最爱的点心呢
That's my favorite snack.
而且内裤无裆 让你少吃点碳水化合物
Yeah, and they're crotchless, so less carbs.
还有我最爱的可微波润滑液
Oh, and my favorite microwavable lube.
这是什么
And what's this?
牙刷吗
Toothbrushes?
你会疼的吧 不过你喜欢就好
Oh, that's going to hurt you, but okay.
不 我是想把这些留在你家
No, I want to leave them at your house,
毕竟我们俩现在是专属情人了
Now that you and I are exclusive.
专属情人吗
Exclusive?
等等 我先问清
Wait, hold phone.
你觉得我们俩还没到
Are you telling me that you and I
专属情人的地步吗
are not exclusive?
专属情人吗
Exclusive?
哎哟 逗死我了
Oh, come on.
要被你逗死了 接着说笑啊
Stop it now. Go on Jay Leno.
卡洛琳 你觉得我和苏菲到专属对方的地步了吗
Caroline, did you think Sophie and I were exclusive?
你现在的确是不对我们露鸟了
Well, you have stopped showing us your penis.
就是嘛
Exactly!
这都不算对你一心一意 那什么才算
If that's not exclusive, I don't know what is.
还一心一意呢
Exclusive!
我要笑死了
Oh, my God.
别逗我了 不然我要...
Oh, come on, stop it, before I--
来不及了
It happened.
我的塑身衣笑崩了
I split my spanx.
请接玛莎·斯图尔特
Martha Stewart, please.
我是米歇尔·奥巴马[美国总统夫人]
It's Michelle Obama.
找她什么事吗
What's this about?
我的床单洗缩水了 老娘很不爽
My sheets shrunk and I am pissed.
还在吗
Hello?
你假装是米克·贾格尔说
Max, it didn't work when you were Mick Jagger
你的松饼托烤坏了 没用
with a busted muffin tin,
装艾丽西亚·凯斯说浴帘摇摇欲坠也没用
Or Alicia Keys with a wonky shower curtain.
你假装是死而复生的史蒂夫·贾伯斯
And it really didn't work when you were Steve jobs
说要指点她的三明治机 更没人理你
back from the dead with thoughts on her panini press.
别在清醒时 一直打电话骚扰人家了
Stop sober dialing Martha Stewart!
谁说我清醒了
Who says I'm sober?
麦克斯 你的手机给我
Max, give me your phone.
老娘的"奶"昔招蜂引蝶一流 *
* My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard.
把我的手机换给我
Now give me my phone.
拿去 行了吧
Okay, take it, done.
我看开了
I'm over her.
她什么时候才会打给我啊
When is she gonna call me?
我的"奶"昔一定能把她招来的
My milkshake would totally bring her to the yard.
麦克斯 这不像你啊
Max, this isn't you.
你是女强人
I mean, you're strong.
女硬汉
You're a badass.
你吃止痛药就能消灭乳突病毒了
You beat H.P.V. with tylenol.
而且你是吃的还是杂牌货
And it wasn't even the name brand.
你这是怎么回事
What's wrong with you?
玛莎破了我的处 行了吧
I was a virgin before Martha, okay?
在她之前 从来没有人夸过我行
No one ever told me I was good at anything before her.
人生"第一个"大款白女人哪能说忘就忘
And you never forget your first rich white woman.
无论有没有她的帮忙
With or without Martha Stewart,
我们都会建立起自己的小蛋糕生意
We're gonna build our cupcake business
然后飞黄腾达 我看得见那未来
And be a success, I just know it.
你怎么看得到 你怎么能肯定
How? How do you know that?
那是因为我知道你有天赋
I know because you have the talent,
我有洞察力 因为我能感觉到成功在望
I have the vision, and because I feel it.
打从心里感觉到
I feel it here.
恶心啊 还你的心呢
Oh, blegh! Your heart?
不是啦 是我的幸运珍珠项链
No. My pearls- my lucky pearls.
是幸运还是丑爆啊
By lucky, do you mean ugly?
自从我被驱逐出我家之后
I've worn these every day
我就天天戴着它
since I was evicted from my townhouse.
这珍珠项链给我带来好运
This pearl necklace brings me luck.
你...
You--
你觉得你好运吗
You think your life is lucky?
今早你用厕纸当咖啡机滤纸
This morning you used toilet paper as a coffee filter...
滤完之后再拿回去当厕纸用
and then used it as toilet paper.
我知道你觉得我白痴
I know this sounds silly to you,
但每天我只要一戴上
But there is something about
我的珍珠项链
putting on these pearls every day
就会觉得自己既坚强又自信
that makes me feel strong, confident,
好像一切皆有可能
and like anything is possible.
而只要我还有幸运项链的陪...
And as long as I have these lucky--
不是吧 不是吧
Oh, no. Oh, no!
别别别 别恐慌
No, no, no, don't freak out.
别恐慌 我们快捡回来
Don't freak out. We'll get em.
我的珍珠
My pearls!
我的幸运珍珠
My lucky pearls!
是是是 我们知道有什么麻烦
Yes, yes, we have identified the problem.
快动手捡起来吧
Just pick them up.
看来有人先行享用早餐啦
Looks like somebody found breakfast.
栗宝 不可以
No, chestnut!
这锅我会继续拿来做哦
I'm still using that.
现在做什么都是徒劳无功
Well, nothing's gonna work out now.
厄运已经降临了
Here comes the bad luck.
说什么傻话
Don't be ridiculous.
你本来就衰到不能再衰了
Your luck couldn't get any worse.
原来真的一切皆有可能
Or could it?
你看 厄尔
Okay, Earl.
这是L-520点菜系统触控板
This is the L-520 order system touch pad.
你看有多简单 瞧
Look how simple. See?
你听我说
I'm telling you,
我学不会这复杂的玩意
I can't figure this tricky little thing out.
厄尔 刚才的是开关钮
Earl, it's an on/off button.
不会吧
Oh, slow down.
那一键还两用啊
It does both?
我先帮把这宝贝充上电吧
Let me just charge this up for you right here.
这块插线板
This thing has been plugged
比卡戴珊姐妹被"插"得还满啊
more than the Kardashian sisters.
我还是先检查一下餐馆这老电路吧
I better check the old wiring in diner first.
麦克斯 我现在感觉大家都在
Max, now I feel like everyone's staring
盯着我胸口看
at my chest area.
欢迎来到我的世界
Well, welcome to my life,
我九岁之后就过着这样的生活
Every day since I was nine.
那珍珠项链对我有特别意义
That necklace meant something special to me.
难道你没有失去过你拥有很久
Didn't you ever lose anything sentimental
感情深厚的事物吗
you had for a long time?
我妈啊 不过后来她又自己跑回来了
My mother, but then she found her way back.
我受够了一直等她回电
Look, I am done waiting for Martha to call.
不如我们再做点蛋糕去找她
I say we go down there with some cupcakes,
提醒她当初她有多喜欢它们
remind her how much she liked them,
然后建议她邀请我们上她节目
and suggest she puts us on her show.
不行 我珍珠都没了怎么去见人啊
No, I mean, I can't go without my pearls.
它不仅仅代表着好运
And it's more than just the luck.
还代表着我破产前的身份
It's who I was before I lost everything.
你知道我说
You know how I always say,
"你好 我是卡洛琳·钱宁"时
"Hi, I'm Caroline Channing,"
每次都会摸摸珍珠吧
and then touch my pearls?
我不只是在自我介绍
I'm not just introducing myself.
那也是在提醒我自己
I'm reminding myself.
那让我也提醒你另外一件事吧
Well, let me remind you of something else.
昨天你告诉我
Yesterday you told me
我们能靠着小蛋糕征服全世界呢
we were going to rule the world with cupcakes.
有珍珠撑腰 说话自然气壮
Yeah, that was the pearls talking.
那现在轮到我说了
Okay, well, now I'm talking.
幸运是不存在的
There is no luck.
努力才是硬道理
There is only work.
可你现在只让我想对你使用暴"力"
And right now, you're working my last nerve.
所以我打算自己去找她
So I am going down there myself.
如果她不愿意帮忙
and if Martha won't help me,
我就用擀面棍打爆她膝盖
I'ma bust her kneecaps with a rolling pin
然后说"这样才是一件好事"
and then say, "now that's a good thing."
这样吧 我们给她发封电邮如何
Okay, what if we just send Martha an E-mail,
这样就不用去到她办公楼
so we're not just standing in her office,
求前台放我们进去了
begging some receptionist?
-那样一点屁用都没有 -有用的
- That won't do anything. - Yes, it will.
我超会写商业电邮呢
I craft amazing business E-mails.
我可是沃顿高材生呢
I went to Wharton.
求你嘴下留情 我就剩这点资本了
Please don't, Max. That's all I have left.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max, Caroline, I found something
我在餐馆贸易展览里
at the restaurant trade show
发现了点你们会感兴趣的东西哦
you might be interested in.
我唯一有兴趣的餐馆贸易
The only restaurant trade I'm interested in
就是看能不能把你以物易物走
is if we can exchange you for anybody else.
看了你就不会笑我了
You won't be laughing in a minute.
你看 这是我从最新研发的
Look, it's a cupcake from the new
自助小蛋糕机买来的小蛋糕
state-of-the-art cupcake ATM machine.
人家连锁小蛋糕店打算城里广设这机器
Sprinkles cupcakes plans to be put them everywhere.
很快 大家只需按下按钮
Soon, everyone will be able to just push a button,
无论白天黑夜 随时都能吃到小蛋糕
Day or night, and get the cupcake.
所以我想说的是
So, I guess what I'm saying is,
你们俩可能完了
You might be screwed.
美味可口
Delicious...
不用受气
And no attitude.
坏运气接踵而至
well, more bad luck.
我原本以为你在开玩笑
I thought you were kidding,
但机器真的要取代人类了
but the machines are taking over.
我们斗不过机器
We can't compete with that.
我们的生意完蛋了 游戏结束
The business is done. Game over.
天啊 你这种态度怎么在未来混啊
Man, you are never gonna make it in the future.
人类就应该在此时奋起反击
This is where the humans fight.
我们就应该在此时 向玛莎·斯图尔特示威
This is where we march down to Martha Stewart
要求她帮我们大力宣传
and demand a damn blurb,
这样我们才能跟机器斗
So we can compete with the machines...
就像《终结者2:甜点的觉醒》
Just like in "Terminator 2: rise of the desserts."
好吧 我们去找玛莎
Fine. Let's go see Martha.
她是我们唯一的希望了
She's our only hope.
我的幸运项链没了
My lucky necklace is gone.
我们不能再坐等奇迹发生
We can no longer just wait for magic to happen.
对了 谢谢你啊
Uh, thank you, by the way,
从没告诉我 原本的计划是等天降鸿福
for never telling me that our former plan was magic.
我们向玛莎重新介绍自己 和我们的小蛋糕
We'll just reintroduce ourselves and our cupcakes to Martha
然后让她再次记住我们
and impress her all over again,
虽然现在的我 戴着一条我讨厌的项链
Even though I'm wearing a necklace that I hate.
这项链没个性 没活力 没光泽
It's limp, anemic, and lackluster.
我脖子上戴着的彷佛是奥尔森姐妹
I have an Olsen twin around my neck.
拿着
here.
你这是干嘛
what are you doing?
这样玛莎就能认出我了
so Martha will recognize me.
打扰了 问你两件事
Hi, excuse me. Two questions.
玛莎·斯图尔特的办公室在几楼
Which floor is Martha Stewart on?
我应该拿掉这条项链吗
And should I lose this necklace?
好吧 沉默说明一切
Well, your silence speaks volumes.
你好 我不是疯子
Hi, I'm not crazy,
你可以把楼层告诉我
so you can just tell me the floor number.
15楼 电梯在那边
Elevator right over there, 15th floor,
玛莎·斯图尔特生活媒体公司
Martha Stewart living omnimedia.
有点小兴奋
Just got a little damp.
谢谢你的建议 感觉好多了
Thanks for your help. Feels better.
真聪明 问一个没有脖子的人
Smart, getting necklace advice
你的脖子该不该戴项链
from a guy with no neck.
慢着 那不就是...
Wait. Is that--
那就是阿憨说的小蛋糕自助机
That's the cupcake machine that han was talking about.
天啊
Ugh, no!
我还希望它会很丑呢
I was hoping it'd be ugly,
但它居然是粉色 而且很可爱
but it's pink and really cute.
就像一台基佬版的R2-D2
It's like a gay R2-D2.
R2-D2已经够基了 它更基一筹
Well, a gayer R2-D2.
谁会想吃从这玩意出来的小蛋糕啊
Who wouldn't want a cupcake from this?
没人
No one.
-我们要给它点"颜色"看看 -什么
- We have to mess her up. - What?
你怎么会在包里随身带着喷漆呢
Why are you carrying spray-paint in your purse?
跟我随身带卫生棉条是一个道理
For the same reason I carry a tampon.
以备不时之需嘛
'cause you never know.
我们不能破坏人家的东西
We are not gonna destroy someone else's property.
我们必需得做点什么啊
Well, we have to do something,
我们不搞死它 它就会玩死我们
'cause it's that machine or us.
我知道了
Oh, I know.
我们可以打开那扇小门 放坨屎进去
We can open the little door and put a poop in it.
当然不是我的啦 天啊
Not one of mine. Jeez!
你把我当成什么了 猪吗
What am I, a pig?
反正我是不干
Well, I'm not doing it.
不是啦 我们可以从大街上捡点狗屎回来
No, we just get some puppy poop from the street.
不要
No!
我们没绝望到那种程度
We are not that desperate.
而且我的湿巾纸用完了
And I'm out of wetnaps.
不是的 我们以前跟玛莎见过面
No, see, we already met Martha.
现在只是过来跟她问声好
We're just stopping by to say hi.
你们以前跟玛莎见过面
You've already met Martha.
-现在只是过来跟她问声好 -对
- You're just stopping by to say hi. - Yes.
玛莎·斯图尔特要了我们的名片
Martha Stewart asked us for our card.
玛莎·斯图尔特要了你们的名片
Martha Stewart asked you for your card.
那我能问下玛莎在哪里要了你们的名片吗
And where should I tell Martha she asked for your card?
女厕所
In the ladies' room.
玛莎·斯图尔特在女厕所要了你们的名片
Martha Stewart asked you for your card in the ladies' room.
好吧
Okay.
别说得好像是我们瞎掰的 事实就是如此
Don't make it sound like that. It happened.
我们在女厕所堵她 然后...
We cornered her in the ladies' room and--
好了 也别说成是这样
okay, don't make it sound like that either.
我们去晚会上碰运气
We went to a gala on the off chance
希望玛莎能和蔼地尝一个
that she would be gracious enough
我们做的小蛋糕 结果她的确尝了
to try one of our cupcakes and she did.
她十分和蔼可亲
She was very gracious.
对啊 或许"堵"这个词用得不太对
Yeah, maybe cornered was the wrong word.
我们又不是去那里追捕她
It's not like we went there to hunt her down.
你们又不是去那里追捕她
it's not like you went there to hunt her down.
真的不是
It's not.
好吧 我听出你的语气
Okay, I hear your tone.
知道你的把戏是什么了
I see what's going down here.
你觉得我们是来找麻烦的
You think I'm some kind of a problem.
我要声明一句 是玛莎先撩我的
Well, for the record, Martha came on to me.
好吧 算了
All right. Okay.
此行不如我们预期般顺利
This is not going as well as we had hoped.
没了我的魔法项链 果然一事无成
Don't know how it could without my magic pearls.
好吧 听着
Okay, look.
我明白你不会放我们进去
I get that you're not gonna let us up there.
我也不怪你
And I don't blame you,
因为这家伙在扯什么魔法
what, with this one talking about magic.
但我得澄清 我们没有说谎
But just so you know, we are not lying.
确有此事
It happened.
在我们逮到她后
And after we hunted her down--
没错 是你让我们不得不说出实话
Because, yeah, you got us on that, we did--
玛莎对我们说
Martha told us
她喜欢我们俩白手起家的精神
she liked our entrepreneurial drive.
这话的确像是玛莎会说的
Well, that does sound like Martha.
好吧 我帮你们送上去 先请坐吧
Okay, I'll send these up. Have a seat.
太谢谢你了
Ahh, thank you so much.
给 你拿一个试试吧
And here, uh, please take one,
这样你也能亲自验证下
Just so you can see for yourself
为什么玛莎会要我们的名片
why Martha asked for our card.
好吧 我本来也打算等会
Well, I was gonna get a cupcake
去楼下机器弄个小蛋糕吃
from that cute machine downstairs later.
千万别去
Oh, don't.
我听说 "一个小时后"有人会在里面
I heard someone found something nasty in that...
发现怪东西呢
in about an hour.
麦克斯
Max.
这是我们的酒混面粉
And this is our beer batter
加枫蜜培根的特制春假小蛋糕
Maple bacon spring break cupcake.
我知道为什么玛莎会...
I can see why Martha-ow!
什么
What the--
我牙齿裂了
I cracked my tooth!
什么
What? Oh!
什么东西啊 是
What is that? Is it--
是玻璃吗
Is that glass?
不是 是珍珠
No, it's a pearl.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
抱歉 抱歉有屁用
Sorry? You're sorry?
我都戴了11个月的透明矫正器了
I've been wearing invisaligns for 11 months!
我们生意的大突破就此告终
Well, there goes our big break.
如果我的幸运项链在的话 就不会发生这种事了
Never would've happened if I had had my necklace.
你说的是那条有着幸运珍珠
The one with the lucky pearls
结果线断珍珠撒 还掉进面粉糊里
that broke into the batter and that woman
害人家口破血流口水滴的项链吗
just spit into her hand mixed with saliva and blood?
是那条幸运项链吧
That lucky necklace?
对啊
Yes.
借此面对现实吧
Might as well face it.
我们俩只能自食其力
You and I are on our own.
这不只是因为玛莎的这件事
And not just because of Martha either.
而是因为这世上没有所谓的"好运"
Because there is no such thing as good luck.
见都没见过
Never seen it.
所有的幸运物都愚蠢无比
And all lucky charms are stupid,
唯一的例外是"幸运物早餐片"
except for the Lucky Charms,
它奇迹般地好吃
which are magically delicious.
看那台自助小蛋糕机
Look at it over there.
基佬R2-D2都在笑我们了
Gay R2-D2 just laughing at us.
麦克斯 你之前说得对
You were right, Max.
我们俩只能自食其力了
You and I are on our own.
我们只是一家刚起步的小蛋糕店
We're just a little start-up cupcake company
在这乱世中求生存
in a hard, hard world.
我们得亲自动手 扫除面前障碍
And we gotta take matters into our own hands.
掩护我
Cover me.
等等 别啊
Wait, wait, no.
别现在干啊
No, don't do it now.
-警卫就在那里呢 -喂 你
- The guard is right there. - Hey, you!
快住手
Stop that!
怎么会有变态想要乱喷小蛋糕机啊
What kind of freaks deface a cupcake machine?
快跑快跑
Run run run.
行了 停停停 甩掉他了
Okay, stop, stop, stop. We lost him.
你知道你没喷到机器 只喷到了墙吧
You know you only tagged the wall, right?
知道啊 我真是倒霉透了
Yes, I have no luck.
世上没人有好运气
No one has any luck...
除了林赛·罗韩的律师吧 有她这个回头客
with the possible exception of Lindsay Lohan's lawyer.
你看 玛莎在那里
Look, it's Martha!
她要上车了 把小蛋糕递给我
She's getting in that car. Give me the cupcakes.
我要在那个吃到珍珠的女人
I'm going after her before she talks
告状之前先跟她谈谈
to that lady whose mouth we broke.
-麦克斯 别晃坏了小蛋糕 -别担心
- Max, don't jiggle the cupcakes! - Don't worry.
老天啊 上帝啊 耶稣啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
麦克斯 你没事吧
Max, are you all right?
你还好吧
Are you all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
也没骨折
No broken bones,
真是奇迹啊 因为我小时候
which is surprising, because when I was kid,
没钱喝过牛奶补钙
we couldn't afford milk.
我妈唯一买过一次牛奶
Actually the only time my mother bought milk
还是因为牛奶盒上有我的照片呢[失踪儿童]
was when my face was on the side of the carton.
你确定你真的没事吗
Are you sure you're all right?
没事啦
Yeah.
原来世上真的有幸运这么一件事
I guess there is such a thing as luck.
从明晚开始
And tomorrow night
当你再次步入餐厅呢 苏菲
when you come in for takeout, Sophie,
麦克斯只需要轻击这个小东西
All Max has to do is hit this little thing.
如果我可以这么做的话
Well, if I'm allowed to hit little things,
我一定击爆你这个小东西
You're next.
改变令大家都紧张兮兮
Change makes everyone so tense.
厨房现在关了
Kitchen is now closed.
我还有约
I have plans.
重要的约呢
Big plans.
苏菲 我知道
Sophie, I understand
你跟奥列格的关系很复杂
your relationship with Oleg is complicated,
所以我就简单一问
So let's simplify it.
你今晚会在咱楼里做爱吗
Are you having sex in our building tonight,
我需要先戴好耳塞吗
and do I have to wear earplugs?
今晚我独守空闺
I will be alone...
你还是戴着以防万一吧
But wear them anyway.
您好 抱歉 我们关门了
Hi, um, sorry, we're closed.
我不是来吃东西的
I do not wish to eat.
奥列格打电话让我上门
I just got collect call from Oleg.
她说关门了
She said we are closed.
是吗 你哪位啊
Oh? And who are you?
我是你被人废了双腿之前
I'm the last person you will see
见到的最后那个人
before you learn how to walk again.
离奥列格远点
Stay away from Oleg,
不然老娘会把你的肠子从鼻孔拉出
Or I'll pull your intestines out through your nose
然后送给她 当新项链戴
and give them to her to wear as new necklace.
行
Fine.
我走
I will leave.
但我是给你蟒蛇般煞气的双眼面子
But only because you have eyes of a python,
还有我最近貌似尿道感染了
And I have possible U.T.I.
苏菲
Sophie...
你就承认你跟奥列格关系不一般嘛
Why don't you just admit it, you and Oleg?
什么
What?
不是我想要他
It's not like I want him.
只是我家乡那里的习惯是
It's just that where I come from,
我用完了 也绝对不扔
You never throw anything away.
拿去吧 姑娘们
Here you go, ladies.
享受从刷卡的客人身上捞来额外小费吧
Enjoy the extra tips from your credit cards,
因为阿憨一旦按下那个改朝换代的按钮
because when Han flips that switch,
我能给你们的小费[小秘诀]
The only tip I can give you is,
就只剩别天天洗头发了
don't wash your hair every day.
头发会丧失水分的
It dries it out.
好啦 一起迈向未来吧
Okay. Here comes the future.
一 二
One, two--
这破楼真他妈要把我搞死了
This old building sucks me so hard.
恭喜你们俩啦
Congratulations, ladies.
今晚是你们的幸运夜
This is your lucky night.
说到幸运
Speaking of luck,
这些是你的珍珠
here are your pearls.
我找回了绝大多数
I found most of them, but I think
但我猜栗宝吃掉了几颗
Chestnut ate a few.
你之后自己去慢慢"挖掘"吧
You can dig for those later yourself.
麦克斯
Max.
但它是弄回不了原样了
And it won't look the same,
因为你得自己用这便宜烂线穿上
because you have to string them on this cheap-ass wire
这是我在嬉皮串珠店买的
I got at the hipster bead store...
店名叫"得以珠之"
Beading off.
我们可以把厄尔给我们的额外收入
We can add this Earl bonus money
加到小蛋糕生意基金里啊
to our cupcake business total.
加上那150块 咱们离目标
Yeah, that 150 will really put a dent
又迈进了"一大步"呢
in the 250,000 we need.
有志者事竟成嘛
We'll get there, Max.
因为我们有着家政女皇跟小蛋糕机都没有的东西
Because you and I have something Martha Stewart and machines don't.
未缴的账单吗
Unpaid bills?
还是浴室门口地毯上长的小蘑菇
Mushrooms growing on our bathroom rug?
我们有着彼此嘛
No, each other.
哎哟 都认识一年了
Aww, a year later you're still
你还在想着让我有点人性
trying to get me to feel things.
你想知道我觉得
Do you wanna know the real reason
它是幸运项链的真正原因吗
I thought this necklace was so lucky?
遇见你的那天 我就戴着它
I was wearing it the day I met you.
会有多余的珍珠呢
So, I'm gonna have some extras.
你想给自己也做一个吗
Do you wanna make one for yourself?
不用 我有过很多"珍珠项链"了
Nah, I've had plenty of pearl necklaces,
我觉得它们是黏腻而不是幸运
and I find them more sticky than lucky.
麦克斯 玛莎斯图尔特网寄信来了
Max, ms@MarthaStewartinc.Com
"我可没忘了你们俩姑娘哦
"Haven't forgotten about you, girls.
玛莎·斯图尔特"
Martha Stewart."
我才以为人生已经无望
Just when I thought I was out,
她又重燃我希望之火
She pulls me back in again.